Guide to the Rice University Assistant to the President papers: Carl MacDowell, 1963-2001 (bulk 1990-1998) UA 084
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas
- Series II: On Campus - General, 1963 – 2000
  - Vice President for Student Affairs
    - Leadership Rice/Advisory Council, 1997 (Box 142, Folder 7)
    - Marching Owl Band (MOB), 1992-93 (Box 142, Folder 8)
    - Marching Owl Band, 1994 (Box 142, Folder 9)
    - Marching Owl Band, 1995-97 (Box 142, Folder 10)
    - Minority Affairs, 1992-94 (Box 142, Folder 11)
    - Minority Affairs, 1995-96 (Box 142, Folder 12)
    - Minority Affairs/Recruiting and Retention, 1991-92 (Box 142, Folder 13)
    - Minority Affairs/(A Proposal for) Recruiting and Retention, 1991-93 (Box 142, Folder 14)
    - Minority Affairs/(A Proposal for) Recruiting and Retention, 1993-94 (Box 142, Folder 15)
    - Ombudsperson, 1994-95 (Box 142, Folder 16)
    - Orientation, 1994-95 (Box 142, Folder 17)
    - Orientation, 1996 (Box 142, Folder 18)
    - Orientation, 1997-98 (Box 142, Folder 19)
    - Parent's Letters, 1995-96 (Box 143, Folder 1)
    - Parent's Letters, 1996-98 (Box 143, Folder 2)
    - Pre-Law Advising, 1990-91 (Box 143, Folder 3)
    - PRIDE (formerly GALOR), 1993-94 (Box 143, Folder 4)
    - Phi Beta Kappa, 1995-98 (Box 143, Folder 5)
    - Psychiatric Services, 1992 (Box 143, Folder 6)
    - Psychiatric Services, 1995-96 (Box 143, Folder 7)
    - Research Agreement/Strassman, Diana, 1992 (Box 143, Folder 8)
    - Rice College Bowl, 1989-92 (Box 143, Folder 9)
    - Rice Memorial Center (RMC), 1992-93 (Box 143, Folder 10)
    - Rice Memorial Center, 1994-96 (Box 143, Folder 11)
    - Rice Memorial Center, 1995-97 (Box 143, Folder 12)
    - Rice Memorial Center, 1997 (Box 143, Folder 13)
    - Rice Student Volunteer Program (RSVP), 1991-92 (Box 143, Folder 14)
    - RSVP, 1991-93 (Box 143, Folder 15)
    - RSVP, 1994 (Box 143, Folder 16)
    - Sexual Harassment, 1992, 1994 (Box 143, Folder 17)
    - Sexual Harassment, 1997-98 (Box 143, Folder 18)
    - Sister Universities, 1990, 1993 (Box 143, Folder 19)
    - Student Activities, 1991-92 (Box 144, Folder 1)
    - Student Activities, 1993-96 (Box 144, Folder 2)
    - Student Affairs, 1991, 1993-94 (Box 144, Folder 3)
    - Student Association, 1992 (Box 144, Folder 4)
    - Student Association, 1991-96 (Box 144, Folder 5)
    - Student Association, 1996 (Box 144, Folder 6)
    - Student Health Service, 1992-94 (Box 144, Folder 7)
    - Student Health Service, 1993-96 (Box 144, Folder 8)
    - Student Organizations, 1996 (Box 144, Folder 9)
    - Student Organizations, 1997 (Box 144, Folder 10)
    - Study Abroad, 1994-95 (Box 144, Folder 11)
    - Study Abroad, 1996-97 (Box 144, Folder 12)
    - Study Abroad, 1997-98 (Box 144, Folder 13)
    - Tuition Waivers, 1991-92 (Box 144, Folder 14)
    - (Rice) Thresher, 1990-92 (Box 144, Folder 15)
    - (Rice) Thresher, 1994 (Box 144, Folder 16)
    - (Rice) Thresher, 1995-97 (Box 145, Folder 1)
    - (Rice) Thresher, 1997-98 (Box 145, Folder 2)
    - (Rice) Thresher/Holocaust, 1997-98 (Box 145, Folder 3)
    - Valhalla, 1990, 1995-96 (Box 145, Folder 4)
    - Vice President for Student Affairs, 1991-92 (Box 145, Folder 5)
    - Vice President for Student Affairs, 1992-93 (Box 145, Folder 6)
    - Vice President for Student Affairs, 1992-94 (Box 145, Folder 7)
    - Vice President for Student Affairs, 1993-94 (Box 146, Folder 1)
    - Vice President for Student Affairs, 1994-97 (Box 146, Folder 2)
    - Vice President for Student Affairs, 1995-96 (Box 146, Folder 3)
    - Vice President for Student Affairs, 1996-97 (Box 146, Folder 4)
    - Vice President for Student Affairs, 1998-97 (Box 146, Folder 5)
    - Vice President for Student Affairs/Camacho, Job Offer Letter, 1994 (Box 146, Folder 6)
    - Vice President for Student Affairs/Search Committee, 1992-93 (Box 146, Folder 7)
    - Willy's Pub, 1990-1993 (Box 146, Folder 8)
    - Willy's Pub, 1994 (Box 146, Folder 9)
    - Willy's Pub, 1994-95 (Box 146, Folder 10)
- Series III: Off Campus - General, 1982 - 2001
  This series is arranged alphabetically by title of off campus organizations and other groups that were not an immediate part of Rice University. There are also Miscellaneous files located here that are filed by alphabetical letter, i.e., A Miscellaneous, B Miscellaneous, etc.
  - "A" Miscellaneous, 1992 (Box 147, Folder 1)
  - "A" Miscellaneous, 1993-94 (Box 147, Folder 2)
  - "A" Miscellaneous, 1995-98 (Box 147, Folder 3)
  - American Association of University Professors (AAUP), 1992-94, 1997-98 (Box 147, Folder 4)
  - AAUP/Salary and Tenure, 1989, 1993-96 (Box 147, Folder 5)
  - American Academy for Liberal Education, 1998 (Box 147, Folder 6)
  - American Council of Learned Societies, 1993-97 (Box 147, Folder 7)
  - American Council on Education, 1994-97 (Box 147, Folder 8)
  - American Council on Education, 1998-99 (Box 147, Folder 9)
  - American Council on Education/Commission on International Education, 1995 (Box 147, Folder 10)
  - Americans for Fair Taxation, 1997-97 (Box 147, Folder 11)
  - Association of American Colleges and Universities (AAC (Box 147, Folder 12)
  - Association of American Universities (AAU), Correspondence, 1996 (Box 147, Folder 13)
  - AAU, Correspondence, 1997 (Box 147, Folder 14)
  - AAU, Correspondence, Feb. - June 1998 (Box 148, Folder 1)
  - AAU, Correspondence, July - Dec. 1998 (Box 148, Folder 2)
  - AAU, Dean's Meeting, March 29-31, 1998 (Box 148, Folder 3)
  - AAU, Meetings, (Gillis' Trips) October 21-23, 1990, Univ. of PA October 17-19, 1993, Purdue Univ. (Box 148, Folder 4)
  - AAU, Meetings, (Gillis' Trips) October 16-18,1994, Univ. of North Carolina April 17-19, 1994, Washington, D.C. (Box 148, Folder 5)
  - AAU, Meetings, April 23-25, 1995, Washington D,C. (Box 148, Folder 6)
  - AAU, Meetings, October 15-17, 1995, Boulder, CO (Box 148, Folder 7)
  - AAU, Meetings, April 14-16, 1996, Washington, D.C. (Box 149, Folder 1)
  - AAU, Meetings, October 20-22, 1996, Burbank/Pasadena, CA (Box 149, Folder 2)
  - AAU, Meetings, April 13-15, 1997, Washington, D.C. (Box 149, Folder 3)
  - AAU, Meetings, April 19-21, 1998, Washington, D.C. (Box 149, Folder 4)
  - AAU, Meetings, October 18-20, 1998, Berkeley, CA (Box 149, Folder 5)
  - AAU, Meetings, April 18-20, 1999, Washington, D.C. (Box 149, Folder 6)
  - Association of Governing Boards of Universities and Colleges, 1994-95 (Box 149, Folder 7)
  - Association of Texas Colleges and Universities (ATCU), 1995-96 (Box 149, Folder 8)
  - Association of Texas Colleges and Universities, 1997-98 (Box 149, Folder 9)
  - "B" Miscellaneous, 1991-92 (Box 149, Folder 10)
  - "B" Miscellaneous, 1993-94 (Box 149, Folder 11)
  - "B" Miscellaneous, 1996-98 (Box 149, Folder 12)
  - Baylor College of Medicine, 1989-92 (Box 149, Folder 13)
  - Baylor College of Medicine, 1994-96 (Box 149, Folder 14)
  - Baylor College of Medicine, 1997-98 (Box 150, Folder 1)
  - Baylor College of Medicine/Committee for School-Based Minority Student Programs, 1991 (Box 150, Folder 2)
  - Baylor College of Medicine/Transfer of Technology, 1997-98 (Box 150, Folder 3)
  - Biosphere 2 Center, 1997 (Box 150, Folder 4)
  - Boy Scouts, 1996 (Box 150, Folder 5)
  - Boy Scouts, 1997 (Box 150, Folder 6)
  - Breman, Feb. - July 1998 (Box 150, Folder 7)
  - Breman, Aug. 1998-99 (Box 150, Folder 8)
  - Breman/Baden-Wurttemberg, 1997-98 (Box 150, Folder 9)
  - "C" Miscellaneous, 1991-92 (Box 150, Folder 10)
  - "C" Miscellaneous, 1993-95 (Box 150, Folder 11)
  - "C" Miscellaneous, 1996-98 (Box 150, Folder 12)
  - Citizens for an Alternative Tax System, 1993-97 (Box 151, Folder 1)
  - Campus Compact, 1995-98 (Box 151, Folder 2)
  - Coalition for Mutual Respect, 1995 (Box 151, Folder 3)
  - (The) College Board, 1995-97 (Box 151, Folder 4)
  - College Football Association, 1995-97 (Box 151, Folder 5)
  - Committee on Science, Engineering and Public Policy (COSPUP), 1995 (Box 151, Folder 6)
  - Consejo Nacional de Ciencia y Tecnologia (CONACYT), 1995 (Box 151, Folder 7)
  - Consortium on Financing Higher Education (COFHE), Correspondence, 1991 (computer disc included) (Box 151, Folder 8)
  - COFHE, Correspondence, Jan. - Sept. 1992 (Box 151, Folder 9)
  - COFHE, Correspondence, Nov. - Dec. 1992 (Box 151, Folder 10)
  - COFHE, Correspondence, 1993 (Box 152, Folder 1)
  - COFHE, Correspondence, 1994-96 (Box 152, Folder 2)
  - COFHE, Correspondence, 1997 (Box 152, Folder 3)
  - COFHE, Correspondence, Nov. - Jan. - April 1998 (Box 152, Folder 4)
  - COFHE, Correspondence, May - Dec. 1998 (Box 152, Folder 5)
  - COFHE, Correspondence, 1999 (Box 152, Folder 6)
  - COFHE, Meetings, April 23-24, 1992, Assembly, MIT (Box 152, Folder 7)
  - COFHE, Meetings, October 29-30, 1992, Assembly, Northwestern (Box 152, Folder 8)
  - COFHE, Meetings, January 12, 1993, Board of Directors, New York City (Box 152, Folder 9)
  - COFHE, Meetings, May 13-14, 1993, Assembly, Williams College (Box 153, Folder 1)
  - COFHE, Meetings, June 13, 1996, Board of Directors, Georgetown Univ. (Box 153, Folder 2)
  - COFHE, Meetings, October 30, 1996, Annual, New York City (Box 153, Folder 3)
  - COFHE, Meetings, November 11-12, 1996, Assembly, Univ. of PA (Box 153, Folder 4)
  - COFHE, Meetings, February 10, 1997, Board of Directors, Teleconference (Box 153, Folder 5)
  - COFHE, Meetings, April 17-18, 1997, Assembly, Oracle, AZ (Box 153, Folder 6)
  - COFHE, Meetings, June 19, 1997, Board of Directors, Georgetown Univ. (Box 153, Folder 7)
  - COFHE, November 3-4, 1997, Assembly, Dartmouth College (Box 153, Folder 8)
  - COFHE, Meetings, November 13, 1997, Annual, Washington D.C. (Box 153, Folder 9)
  - COFHE, Meetings, April 20-21, 1998, Assembly, Trinity College (Box 153, Folder 10)
  - COFHE, Meetings, April 14, 1998, Board of Directors, Branard College (Box 153, Folder 11)
  - COFHE, Meetings, Spring 1998, Assembly (Box 154, Folder 1)
  - COFHE, Meetings, June 18, 1998, Board of Directors, Branard College (Box 154, Folder 2)
  - COFHE, Meetings, October 5-6, 1998, Carleton College (Box 154, Folder 3)
  - COFHE, Meetings, October 27, 1998, Annual/Board of Directors, New York City (Box 154, Folder 4)
  - Consulates, 1994-96 (Box 154, Folder 5)
  - Consulates, 1997-98 (Box 154, Folder 6)
  - Cotton Bowl, 1994-95 (Box 154, Folder 7)
  - Council for Advancement and Support of Education (CASE), 1995- 96 (Box 154, Folder 8)
  - Council on Competitiveness, 1988, 1993-95 (Box 154, Folder 9)
  - Council on Governmental Relations, 1995 (Box 154, Folder 10)
  - Council on Governmental Relations, 1996 (Box 154, Folder 11)
  - Council on Governmental Relations, 1997 (Box 154, Folder 12)
  - "D" Miscellaneous, 1992, 1995-96 (Box 154, Folder 13)
  - Department of Education, 1995-96 (Box 154, Folder 14)
  - Department of Education, 1998 (Box 154, Folder 15)
  - Department of Education/State Postsecondary Review Program (SPRE), 1993-May 1994 (Box 154, Folder 16)
  - Department of Education/SPRE, July - Dec. 1994 (Box 155, Folder 1)
  - Department of Education, 1995-96, 1998 (Box 155, Folder 2)
  - "E" Miscellaneous, 1991-92, 1994-95 (Box 155, Folder 3)
  - Ernst and Young, Center for Process Innovation, 1995-96 (Box 155, Folder 4)
  - Events – Outside,1997-98 (Box 155, Folder 5)
  - "F" Miscellaneous, 1991-92, 1995-96 (Box 155, Folder 6)
  - Fermilab, 1996-97 (Box 155, Folder 7)
  - Foreign Language Instruction, 1988, 1990 (Box 155, Folder 8)
  - "G" Miscellaneous, 1996-98, n. d. (Box 156, Folder 1)
  - Governmental File, 1991-92 (Box 156, Folder 2)
  - Governmental File, 1994, 1996-97 (Box 156, Folder 3)
  - Greater Houston Partnership, 1990, 1995-96 (Box 156, Folder 4)
  - Greater Houston Partnership, 1997 (Box 156, Folder 5)
  - Greater Houston Partnership, 1998 (Box 156, Folder 6)
  - Greater Houston Partnership/Marcoa Article, 1997 (Box 156, Folder 7)
  - "H" Miscellaneous, 1991-92, 1995 (Box 156, Folder 8)
  - "H" Miscellaneous, 1997-98 (Box 156, Folder 9)
  - Hamilton Taft and Company, 1991 (Box 156, Folder 10)
  - Harvard Institute for International Development (HIID), 1995-97 (Box 156, Folder 11)
  - Harvard University, 1992, 1994-96, 1998 (Box 156, Folder 12)
  - Houston Advanced Research Center (HARC), 1990, 1992 (Box 156, Folder 13)
  - HARC, 1993 (Box 157, Folder 1)
  - HARC, 1994 (Box 157, Folder 2)
  - HARC, 1995-97 (Box 157, Folder 3)
  - Houston Area Survey, 1996 (Box 157, Folder 4)
  - Houston Business Review, 1997 (Box 157, Folder 5)
  - Houston Chronicle, 1995-98 (Box 157, Folder 6)
  - Houston, City of, 1995-96 (Box 157, Folder 7)
  - Houston Community College System (HCCS), 1995 (Box 157, Folder 8)
  - Houston Committee on Foreign Relations, 1995 (Box 157, Folder 9)
  - Houston Endowment, Inc. 1979-89 (Box 157, Folder 10)
  - Houston Endowment, Inc., 1990-92 (Box 157, Folder 11)
  - Houston Independent School District (HISD), 1995, 1997-98 (Box 157, Folder 12)
  - Houston Metropolitan Study, 1997 (Box 157, Folder 13)
  - Houston Technology Center, 1997 (Box 157, Folder 14)
  - Hugh O'Brien Youth Foundation (HOBY), 1992-95 (Box 158, Folder 1)
  - Hugh O'Brien Youth Foundation, 1996 (Box 158, Folder 2)
  - Hugh O'Brien Youth Foundation/World Leadership Congress, 1996 (Box 158, Folder 3)
  - Hugh O'Brien Youth Foundation/World Leadership Congress- Briefing Book, 1996 (Box 158, Folder 4)
  - "I" Miscellaneous, 1996-98 (Box 158, Folder 5)
  - Independent Colleges and Universities of Texas (ICUT), 1988, 1990-91 (Box 158, Folder 6)
  - ICUT, 1992 (Box 158, Folder 7)
  - ICUT, 1993 (Box 159, Folder 1)
  - ICUT, 1994 (Box 159, Folder 2)
  - ICUT, 1995 (Box 159, Folder 3)
  - ICUT, 1996 (Box 159, Folder 4)
  - ICUT, 1997 (Box 160, Folder 1)
  - ICUT, 1998 (Box 160, Folder 2)
  - Independent Colleges and Universities of Texas/Annual Meeting, 1998 (Box 160, Folder 3)
  - Institute for Policy Reform, 1993-94 (Box 160, Folder 4)
  - Institute of International Education (IIE), 1992, 1994 (Box 160, Folder 5)
  - IIE, 1995 (Box 160, Folder 6)
  - IIE, 1996-97 (Box 160, Folder 7)
  - International Alliance for Higher Education, 1994-95 (Box 160, Folder 8)
  - International American Educational Centre/A.B.C. University Protocol Agreement, n. d. (Box 160, Folder 9)
  - International Space University, 1996 (Box 160, Folder 10)
  - International Space University, 1997 (Box 160, Folder 11)
  - "J" Miscellaneous, 1992-94 (Box 160, Folder 12)
  - "K" Miscellaneous, 1992, 1994-96 (Box 160, Folder 13)
  - "L" Miscellaneous, 1992-94 (Box 160, Folder 14)
  - Law of the Sea Institute, 1996 (Box 160, Folder 15)
  - Legislative, 1994 (Box 160, Folder 16)
  - Legislative, 1995-96 (Box 161, Folder 1)
  - Legislative, 1997 (Box 161, Folder 2)
  - Legislative/S. B. 153-Ashcroft/Moynihan, 1997 (Box 161, Folder 3)
  - Legislature, Texas, 1995-98 (Box 161, Folder 4)
  - Legislature, Texas/Paul Sadler Texas House Spec Committee on Taxation and Public School Financing, 1997 (Box 161, Folder 5)
  - "M" Miscellaneous, 1992, 1995-96 (Box 161, Folder 6)
  - Marine Discovery Center of Galveston, 1995-96 (Box 161, Folder 7)
  - Microelectronics and Computer Technology Corp. (MCC), John McRary, 1995-96 (Box 161, Folder 8)
  - Money Magazine, 1991-92 (Box 161, Folder 9)
  - Money Magazine, 1993-94 (Box 161, Folder 10)
  - Money Magazine, 1995 (Box 161, Folder 11)
  - "N" Miscellaneous, 1990, 1992, 1994-97 (Box 161, Folder 12)
  - National Academy of Science/Engineering, 1993-94 (Box 161, Folder 13)
  - National Academy of Science/Engineering, 1995-96 (Box 161, Folder 14)
  - National Academy of Science/Engineering, 1997-98 (Box 161, Folder 15)
  - National Aeronautics and Space Administration (NASA), 1991, 1996 (Box 161, Folder 16)
  - NASA, 1997-98 (Box 161, Folder 17)
  - National Association of Independent Colleges and Universities (NAICU), 1995 (Box 161, Folder 18)
  - NAICU, 1996 (Box 161, Folder 19)
  - NAICU, 1997 (Box 161, Folder 20)
  - NAICU, 1998 (Box 161, Folder 21)
  - National Collegiate Athletic Association (NCAA), 1989-91 (Box 162, Folder 1)
  - NCAA, 1992 (Box 162, Folder 2)
  - NCAA, 1993 (Box 162, Folder 3)
  - NCAA, 1994 (Box 163, Folder 1)
  - NCAA, 1995 (Box 163, Folder 2)
  - NCAA, 1996 (Box 163, Folder 3)
  - NCAA, 1997 (Box 163, Folder 4)
  - NCAA, 1998 (Box 163, Folder 5)
  - NCAA/Academic Reporting, 1993-94 (Box 164, Folder 1)
  - NCAA/Convention, 1996 (Box 164, Folder 2)
  - NCAA/Convention, 1997 (Box 164, Folder 3)
  - NCAA/Title IX, 1995 (Box 164, Folder 4)
  - NCAA/Title IX, 1996-98 (Box 164, Folder 5)
  - National Council for Accreditation of Teacher Education (NCATE), 1995-96, 1998 (Box 164, Folder 6)
  - National Institute for the Environment (NIE), 1995, 1998 (Box 164, Folder 7)
  - National Merit Scholarship Corp., 1982, 1990, 1993-95, 1997-99 (Box 164, Folder 8)
  - National Science Board, 1997 (Box 164, Folder 9)
  - National Science Foundation (NSF), 1994-95 (Box 165, Folder 1)
  - NSF, 1996 (Box 165, Folder 2)
  - NSF, 1997-98 (Box 165, Folder 3)
  - NSF/Alliance for Minority Participation (AMP), 1995 (Box 165, Folder 4)
  - National University of Science and Technology (NUST)-Pakistan, 1996 (Box 165, Folder 5)
  - North Harris Montgomery Community College District, 1994-96 (Box 165, Folder 6)
  - "O" Miscellaneous, 1996-97 (Box 165, Folder 7)
  - Organization for Tropical Studies, 1997-98 (Box 165, Folder 8)
  - "P" Miscellaneous, 1991-94 (Box 165, Folder 9)
  - "P" Miscellaneous, 1995-96 (Box 165, Folder 10)
  - "P" Miscellaneous, 1997-98 (Box 165, Folder 11)
  - Powell, Colin, 1995 (Box 165, Folder 12)
  - Prevent Blindness, 1996-97 (Box 165, Folder 13)
  - "R" Miscellaneous, 1992-94 (Box 165, Folder 14)
  - Russian American University Consortium, 1991 (Box 165, Folder 15)
  - Russian Visit/Energy, 1993 (Box 165, Folder 16)
  - "S" Miscellaneous, 1991-94 (Box 166, Folder 1)
  - "S" Miscellaneous, 1995-97 (Box 166, Folder 2)
  - Saigh Charitable Foundation, 1998-99 (Box 166, Folder 3)
  - Savings Bond Campaign, 1995 (Box 166, Folder 4)
  - Savings Bond Campaign, 1996 (Box 166, Folder 5)
  - School Reform, 1997-98 (Box 166, Folder 6)
  - (The) Science Coalition, January 1996-April 1996 (Box 166, Folder 7)
  - (The) Science Coalition, May 1996-November 1996 (Box 166, Folder 8)
  - (The) Science Coalition, 1997 (Box 166, Folder 9)
  - Sewanee, The University of the South, 1997 (Box 166, Folder 10)
  - Soechting Properties, 1994 (Box 166, Folder 11)
  - South Main Center Association (SMCA), 1990-92 (Box 166, Folder 12)
  - South Main Center Association, 1993-94 (Box 166, Folder 13)
  - South Main Center Association, 1995-96 (Box 167, Folder 1)
  - South Main Center Association, 1997-99 (Box 167, Folder 2)
  - South Texas Science Academy (Rice/Baylor/STISD), 1991 (Box 167, Folder 3)
  - Southern Association of Colleges and Schools (SACS), 1985, 1990-91 (Box 167, Folder 4)
  - Southern Association of Colleges and Schools (SACS), 1992 (Box 167, Folder 5)
  - Southern Association of Colleges and Schools (SACS), 1993-94 (Box 167, Folder 6)
  - Southern Association of Colleges and Schools (SACS), 1995 (Box 167, Folder 7)
  - Southern Association of Colleges and Schools (SACS), 1996 (Box 167, Folder 8)
  - Southern Association of Colleges and Schools (SACS), 1997-99 (Box 168, Folder 1)
  - SACS/Emory University Visitation, 1992 (Box 168, Folder 2)
  - SACS/Proceedings (March April), 1992 (Box 168, Folder 3)
  - Southwest Athletic Conference (SWAC), 1987, 1991 (Box 168, Folder 4)
  - Southwest Athletic Conference (SWAC), 1992 (Box 168, Folder 5)
  - Southwest Athletic Conference (SWAC), 1993 (Box 168, Folder 6)
  - Southwest Athletic Conference (SWAC), 1994 (Box 169, Folder 1)
  - Southwest Athletic Conference (SWAC), 1995 (Box 169, Folder 2)
  - Southwest Athletic Conference (SWAC), Jan.-March 1996 (Box 169, Folder 3)
  - Southwest Athletic Conference (SWAC), May 1996-97 (Box 169, Folder 4)
  - SWAC/President's Council Meeting, 1990 (Box 169, Folder 5)
  - SWAC/Press, 1993-95 (Box 170, Folder 1)
  - Superconducting Super Collider, 1990-91 (Box 170, Folder 2)
  - Superconducting Super Collider, 1992-93 (Box 170, Folder 3)
  - "T" Miscellaneous, 1991-92 (Box 170, Folder 4)
  - "T" Miscellaneous, 1993-95 (Box 170, Folder 5)
  - "T" Miscellaneous, 1996-98 (Box 170, Folder 6)
  - Taxpayer Relief Act of 1997, 1997 (Box 170, Folder 7)
  - Texas A M, 1992-94 (Box 170, Folder 8)
  - Texas Air Control Board, 1992 (Box 170, Folder 9)
  - Texas Council on Economic Education, 1997-98 (Box 170, Folder 10)
  - Texas Equalization Grant (TEG), 1994-97 (Box 170, Folder 11)
  - Texas Higher Education Coordinating Board, 1992-94 (Box 170, Folder 12)
  - Texas Higher Education Coordinating Board, 1996 (Box 170, Folder 13)
  - Texas Higher Education Coordinating Board, 1997-98 (Box 170, Folder 14)
  - Texas Independent College Fund (TICF), 1991 (Box 171, Folder 1)
  - TICF, 1992 (Box 171, Folder 2)
  - TICF, 1993 (Box 171, Folder 3)
  - TICF, 1994 (Box 171, Folder 4)
  - TICF, 1995 (Box 171, Folder 5)
  - TICF, 1996 (Box 171, Folder 6)
  - TICF, 1997 (Box 171, Folder 7)
  - TICF, 1998 (Box 171, Folder 8)
  - Texas Medical Center, 1995, 1998 (Box 171, Folder 9)
  - Texas Medical Center/Adjunct Faculty, 1995 (Box 171, Folder 10)
  - Texas Medical Center/Flooding, 1997-98 (Box 171, Folder 11)
  - Texas Space Grant Consortium, 1990-91 (Box 172, Folder 1)
  - Trinity Tuition Exchange, 1992 (Box 172, Folder 2)
  - "U" Miscellaneous, 1991-92 (Box 172, Folder 3)
  - "U" Miscellaneous, 1993 (Box 172, Folder 4)
  - "U" Miscellaneous, 1995, 1997-98 (Box 172, Folder 5)
  - U. S./Mexico Attorney General Meeting, 1995 (Box 172, Folder 6)
  - U. S. News and World Report, 1991-92 (Box 172, Folder 7)
  - U. S. News and World Report, 1996-97 (Box 172, Folder 8)
  - U. S. News and World Report, 1998 (Box 172, Folder 9)
  - United Way, 1995-96 (Box 172, Folder 10)
  - United Way, 1997-98 (Box 172, Folder 11)
  - Universities/Comparative Data, 1996-97 (Box 172, Folder 12)
  - Universities/Miscellaneous, 1991 (Box 172, Folder 13)
  - Universities/Miscellaneous, Jan.-Oct. 1992 (Box 172, Folder 14)
  - Universities/Miscellaneous, Nov.-Dec. 1992 (Box 172, Folder 15)
  - Universities/Miscellaneous, 1993-94 (Box 173, Folder 1)
  - Universities/Miscellaneous, 1997 (Box 173, Folder 2)
  - Universities/Rankings, 1998 (Box 173, Folder 3)
  - Universities Research Association, 1993-94 (Box 173, Folder 4)
  - Universities Research Association, 1995 (Box 173, Folder 5)
  - Universities Research Association, 1996-98, 2001 (Box 173, Folder 6)
  - University of Houston, 1991-94 (Box 173, Folder 7)
  - University of Houston, 1995-96 (Box 173, Folder 8)
  - University of Houston, 1997 (Box 173, Folder 9)
  - University of Houston/Texas Center for University School Partnerships, 1990-91 (Box 173, Folder 10)
  - University of Texas, 1987 (Box 173, Folder 11)
  - University of Texas, 1991 (Box 173, Folder 12)
  - University of Texas, 1995-96 (Box 173, Folder 13)
  - University of Texas Health Science Center at Houston, 1991 (Box 173, Folder 14)
  - University of Texas Health Science Center at Houston/Rice-Joint Affiliation, 1983, 1985-86 (Box 173, Folder 15)
  - University Writing Course, 1993 (Box 173, Folder 16)
  - Urban League, 1994 (Box 173, Folder 17)
  - "V" – "Y" Miscellaneous, 1991, 1993-94 (Box 173, Folder 18)
  - "W" Miscellaneous, 1991-93, 1997 (Box 173, Folder 19)
  - Wartsila/Metra Meeting, 1997 (Box 173, Folder 20)
  - Washington, D.C., 1994-95 (Box 173, Folder 21)
  - Weingarten Realty Investors, 1986-87 (Box 173, Folder 22)
  - Western Athletic Conference (WAC), 1993-94 (Box 174, Folder 1)
  - WAC, 1995 (Box 174, Folder 2)
  - WAC, Jan.-June 1996 (Box 174, Folder 3)
  - WAC, July-Dec. 1996 (Box 174, Folder 4)
  - WAC, Jan.-May 1997 (Box 174, Folder 5)
  - WAC, June-Dec. 1997 (Box 175, Folder 1)
  - WAC, Jan.-April 1998 (Box 175, Folder 2)
  - WAC, May 1998 (Collapse) (Box 175, Folder 3)
  - WAC, June 1998 (Collapse) (Box 175, Folder 4)
  - WAC, July 1998 (Box 175, Folder 5)